justguys.net 2018-12-28

# JustGuys.net Privacy Policy

**[JustGuys.net](http://www.justguys.net/) PRIVACY POLICY**

1\. Your privacy is our biggest concern on this site and every possible effort has been and is being made to provide you with a safe, secure and private environment that you control.  

2\. Information Gathered  
When you register as a member and set up a profile certain personal information is required and asked of you. This includes your email address, age, pictures, description, and location information. This information is stored on our systems, but NEVER shared or leased to third parties. It is our strict policy NEVER to share ANY of this personal information with third parties.   

3\. Use of Information  
Your personal information gathered on this site will be used for statistical and demographics use only. Your email or any other private information will not be shared with, sold or leased to any third party. Only authorized personnel of Century Media Group, Inc. will have access to this information. Additionally, your information may be used internally by authorized staff only to improve our services, analyze site usage, optimize content, etc.  

4\. Your Password  
It is vital that your keep your password safe to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information. If you believe that your password has been compromised for any reason please CHANGE it immediately.  

5\. Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that allows us to recognize your computer in our system. You will have the option of having the system ‘remember you’ to avoid re-entering login and password every time. However, if you desire a higher level of security, we suggest not checking the ‘remember me’ box.  

6\. Removing Your Profile   
You have the option to remove your profile. Please note that this will remove your profile from our website, but will allow you to re-instate your profile for up to one month. After this time, your profile information will be permanently deleted from our systems. No data will remain on our systems with the exception of personal correspondence or support enquiries sent to us, which may be stored on file.  

7\. Online Correspondence and Private Messages  
We do not prescreen your private messages to other members and emails through our internal mail system. However, we reserve the right to monitor any member’s mail or messages to insure that Terms of Service are being followed. Any correspondence sent to us, including emails, will be stored on file and accessible only to authorized staff.  

8\. Disclosure of Your Information  
· We will not disclose any of your information beyond your profile without your permission. 

· We will not sell or rent or pass along your information to any third party. 

· We will only disclose your personal information if legally obligated to do so by a legal authority with the appropriate jurisdiction.  

9\. No Spam Policy  
We do not spam our members. If you were spammed through our site, please notify us along with a copy of suspected spam email so that we can take appropriate action.  

10\. Link Service  
Our site includes various 'link' services. You can choose whether to display your link and profile on the world wide web by clicking on the "account" perferences page. Then choose to share your profile or not, by selecting the appropriate radio button. Profiles are shared by default. Your friends will never receive unsolicited email from us. We have no control over the usage of this service and it is accessible to any member or visitor to our site. You may not use the 'link' services to send spam.  

11\. Our Commitment To Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   

12\. Policy Changes  
If we make any changes to our privacy policy, these changes will be posted to our privacy policy page. You should review this page regularly for updates.
